

JEMIMAH SOLOMON-SANU

UI/UX DESIGNER

I'm a creative UX designer, knowledgeable in UX design tools Figma and Adobe XD. Proficient in Adobe Indesign, Adobe Illustrator, and Adobe

Photoshop. Familiar with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Phython

Django, and Git and Github.

I have Good digital collaboration skills and Great communication skills with clients. Can multitask and still achieve great results.

+234-706-1150-991 Phone:

E-mail: jemimahsolomonsanu@gmail.com LinkedIn: Jemimaholuwaloniisolomonsanu

Github: jemimahsolosanu Portfolio: jemimahsanuportfolio

DESIGN SKILLS

Wireframing and prototyping

Usability studies Design System Product design Information Architecture

User research Interaction Design Visual Design Usability Testing Design Thinking Adobe Creative Suite

Coding: HTML/CSS Responsive Design Accessibility Design

Branding Product Design Digital Marketing Video Editing

TECHNICAL

Figma Adobe XD Adobe Indesign Adobe Photoshop Adobe illustrator HTMI CSS

Filmora (Video editing) Scrum methodology

COLLABORATION

- Adaptability and Flexibility
- Time Management and Prioritization
- Empathy and User-Centered Design
- Decision Making and Strategic Planning - Attention to Detail and Accuracy
- Creativity and Innovation

Certification

2021/06 - 2022/02

Google UX Design Certificate

Google

Completed a rigorous training designed for entry-level job readiness. 15 modules included topics like: UX research fundamentals, inclusive design, low-fidelity and high-fidelity prototypes, and tools like Figma and Adobe XD. Completed hands-on projects and developed a portfolio including 3 projects to receive the certificate.

Projects

Worktracka Mental health mobile app

2022/06

View case study here

Led the development of comprehensive wireframes and navigation maps based on user research and identified user needs. Facilitated multiple user testing sessions with stakeholders to determine design changes and feedback. Researched methods such as interviews, surveys and focus groups to identify user requirements and

2Toren learning app and responsive website design

2022/01

View case study here

Lead UX research while designing the visuals and interactions of the platform from conception to delivery. Conducted interviews, created paper and digital wireframes, Prototyped several iterations based on insights gathered from market testing.

Snottie's note-taking website UI/UX design

2021/11

, View case study here

Designed a website to be user friendly by providing clear note-taking process. I served as the UX designer, from conception to delivery. Conducted interviews, created paper and digital wireframes, low and high-fidelity prototypes, conducted usability studies, accounted for accessibility, and iterated on designs.

VIG Bakery and payment mobile app

2021/09

View case study here

Designed an app for Vig's bakery from conception to delivery. Served as the UX designer, Conducted interviews, created paper and digital wireframes, low and high-fidelity prototypes, conducted usability studies, accounted for accessibility, and iterated on designs.

Work History

2011/10 - Present

Graphic/UI/UX Designer (Freelance)

Pinon Excellent Creations

Consult with clients to establish the overall look, graphic elements and content of communication materials in order to meet their needs. Coordinate all aspects of production for print, audio-visual and electronic materials such as Websites, ebooks, and interactive media. Created wireframes, prototyping, storyboards, user persona.

2011/11 - Present

Branding and Graphics Designer (Freelance)

Adonai Consults, USA

Design for contents for electronic productions such as multimedia, interactive and digital products, publications, and website design.

Training

Full-Stack Development

2024/05 - 2024/07

Sabi Programmers, Akure. Ondo State

Programming languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Phython. Framework: Django Git and Github

Education

Bachelors degree

2013/06 - 2017/04

Obafemi Awolowo University, Ile-Ife, Osun State. Nigeria - Fine and Applied Arts (Graphic Design)

Graduated with 2:1 GPA (Second class upper)

National Diploma

2010/09 - 2012/11

Auchi Polytechnic, Auchi. Edo State. Nigeria - Industrial Arts and Design

Graduated with 2:1 GPA (Upper division)